.::LiveCareer

Resume Heading

We suggest including an email and phone number.



GAYUSHI5038@GMAIL.CO

9389998071

⊙ AGRA, India 282003

LINKS

- https://github.com/07a yushi
- https://www.linkedin.co m/in/ayushi-gupta-9579991b3/
- https://www.behance.n et/ayushigupta13

EDUCATION

B.Tech: Electronics And Communications Engineering JSS ACADEMY oF TECHNICAL EDUCATION, NOIDA, Expected in June 2022

Class XII **SRGMSS**, Agra, March 2017

AYUSHI GUPTA

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Solution-driven Web Developer adept at contributing to highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions and determining customer satisfaction. Proven experience developing consumer-focused websites using HTML, CSS and JavaScript. Built products for desktop and mobile app users, meeting highest standards for web design, user experience, best practices and speed. Designed and developed web applications across multiple APIs, third-party integrations and databases.

SKILLS

- Web development projects
- HTML,HTML5
- CSS,SCSS,BOOTSTRAP
- Programming Languages:
 C,C++,Python
- Data Structures and Algorithms, Problem Solving
- Project Management

- JavaScript, React, Redux
- Databases: SQL,PostgreSQL,MongoDB
- Backend : Node.js , express
- OpenCV
- Data Analysis, Data Visualisation
- Adobe illustrator, photoshop, xD, inDesign

WORK HISTORY

September 2020 - March 2021 **Virtual Creations India - Freelance Web Designer**, AGRA, India

- Utilize Adobe Creative Suite, Photoshop and illustrator on Apple Macintosh hardware to deliver high quality work on tight schedules.
- Sourcing, compositing, and retouching images for print and web.
- Planned website development, converting mockups into usable web presence with HTML, JavaScript, AJAX and JSON coding.

October 2020 - December 2020 kanikka - Graphic Design Intern,





BACK

SAVE & NEXT



GAYUSHI5038@GMAIL.CO M

9389998071

⊙ AGRA, India 282003

LINKS

- https://github.com/07a yushi
- https://www.linkedin.co m/in/ayushi-gupta-9579991b3/
- https://www.behance.n et/ayushigupta13

EDUCATION

B.Tech: Electronics And Communications Engineering JSS ACADEMY oF TECHNICAL EDUCATION, NOIDA, Expected in June 2022

Class XII **SRGMSS**, Agra, March 2017

AYUSHI GUPTA

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Solution-driven Web Developer adept at contributing to highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions and determining customer satisfaction. Proven experience developing consumer-focused websites using HTML, CSS and JavaScript. Built products for desktop and mobile app users, meeting highest standards for web design, user experience, best practices and speed. Designed and developed web applications across multiple APIs, third-party integrations and databases.

SKILLS

- Web development projects
- HTML,HTML5
- CSS,SCSS,BOOTSTRAP
- Programming Languages:
 C,C++,Python
- Data Structures and Algorithms, Problem Solving
- Project Management

- JavaScript, React, Redux
- Databases: SQL,PostgreSQL,MongoDB
- Backend : Node.js , express
- OpenCV
- Data Analysis, Data Visualisation
- Adobe illustrator, photoshop, xD, inDesign

WORK HISTORY

September 2020 - March 2021 **Virtual Creations India - Freelance Web Designer**, AGRA, India

- Utilize Adobe Creative Suite, Photoshop and illustrator on Apple Macintosh hardware to deliver high quality work on tight schedules
- Sourcing, compositing, and retouching images for print and web.
- Planned website development, converting mockups into usable web presence with HTML, JavaScript, AJAX and JSON coding.

October 2020 - December 2020 kanikka - Graphic Design Intern,